International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Southington Lodge 1746A Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Southington Lodge 1746A Records
undated, 1964-1989.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Industrial Aircraft Lodge 1746A (Southington, Conn.)
54.85 linear feet.
MSS19900040
The Industrial Aircraft Lodge 1746A of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW) is affiliated with the AFL-CIO. The Local represents production workers at United Technologies Corporation's Pratt and Whitney plant in Southington, Connecticut. Lodge members work at the Pratt and Whitney plant in East Hartford, Connecticut. Workers at both plants make jet engines and components for commercial and military aircraft. Lodge 1746A is a member of IAMAW District 91. The IAMAW Grand Lodge headquarters are in Washington, D.C.
History
The Industrial Aircraft Lodge 1746A of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW) is affiliated with the AFL-CIO. The Local represents production workers at United Technologies Corporation's Pratt and Whitney plant in Southington, Connecticut. Lodge members work at the Pratt and Whitney plant in East Hartford, Connecticut. Workers at both plants make jet engines and components for commercial and military aircraft. Lodge 1746A is a member of IAMAW District 91. The IAMAW Grand Lodge headquarters are in Washington, D.C.
According to the 1974 and 1977 constitutions of IAMAW, the union is open to both male and female employees. Any machinist, die sinker, die or tool maker, aerospace worker, electronic worker, automobile, heavy duty or aircraft machinist or mechanic, welder, specialist, machinist's helper, production worker, helper-apprentice, or apprentice working in the machine or metal industry can be admitted to the membership upon paying the required fee and by assuming the obligation of the International Association of Machinists. Members cannot advocate or encourage communism, fascism, Nazism, or any other totalitarian philosophy or give support to those philosophies.
Scope and Content
The IAMAW, Lodge 1746A collection contains union business records from 1964-1983 (bulk 1979-1983), including correspondence, contracts, by-laws, publications, minutes, financial and administrative records.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series. Most of the records in the collection are in their original file folders. Only file folders in poor condition have been replaced.
Series I: By-Laws and Contracts ( undated, 1969-1982 ) contains contracts, the by-laws of Lodge 1746A, and the constitutions of the Connecticut State AFL-CIO and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers. The by-laws discuss the name of Lodge 1746A, its meetings, membership, fees and dues, nomination and election of officers, the executive board, and committees. The contracts between the AFL-CIO and Lodge 1746A outline job and facility procedures, wages, benefits, the grievance procedure, military service, and other topics. This series is arranged chronologically.
Series II: Minutes ( 1964-1983 ) includes executive board and membership meeting minutes. The minutes cover by-law changes, purchases, social events such as the lodge Christmas party, and business reports on layoffs, terminations, and other problems. This series is arranged chronologically.
Series III: Office Files ( 1970-1983 ) is the most complete series. It contains financial records, incoming and outgoing correspondence, reports, seniority lists, termination, news clippings, press releases, negotiations and agreements, photographs, Grand Lodge minutes and fiscal information, Connecticut State Council of Machinists executive board minutes, and minutes of the Meriden and Bristol Labor Councils. A recurring theme in this series is correspondence to the IAMAW hierarchy and Lodge 91. The series is arranged chronologically, and alphabetically within each year.
Series IV: Publications ( 1970-1982 ) consists of Lodge 1746A Union Bulletins, and IAMAW, AFL-CIO, and International Metal Workers publications. This series is arranged chronologically.
Series V: Personnel Evaluations ( 1979 ) **RESTRICTED** contains notes, correspondence, and official forms. This series is arranged chronologically by department number.
Series VI: Grievances ( undated, 1970-1989 ) **RESTRICTED** includes grievances, job descriptions, letters, dispositions, grievance reports, grievance summary sheets, rulings, arbitration files, employee service records, and committee reports. The series is arranged chronologically.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of labor related collections. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
Machinists—Job descriptions.; Machinist— Connecticut.; Aircraft industry—Job descriptions.; Aerospace industries𠀔Employees—Labor unions—Connecticut.; Machinists—Labor unions—Connecticut.; Aircraft industry𠀔Employees—Labor unions—Connecticut.; Labor unions—Political activity.; Labor unions—Periodicals.; Labor unions—New England.; Strikes and lockouts—Aircraft industry—Connecticut.; Aircraft industry—Connecticut.; Aircraft industry workers—Connecticut.; Arbitration, Industrial—Connecticut.; Grievance procedures—Connecticut.; Trade-union meetings—Connecticut.; Actions and defenses—Connecticut.; Courts—Connecticut.; Civil law—Connecticut.; Aerospace industries—Connecticut.; East Hartford (Conn.)—Business, industries, and trades—Aircraft.; Southington (Conn.)—Business, industries, and trades—Aircraft.; Connecticut𠀔Labor—Trade-unions.; Connecticut𠀔Labor—Strikes and lockouts.; East Hartford (Conn.)𠀔Labor—Trade-unions.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Photographs.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Press releases.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Scrap-Books.; Lawsuits.
Occupations:
Labor union.
Restrictions on Access
Consult with the Curator for information about access to restricted grievance, arbitration, and case files.
Acquisition Information
The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Industrial Aircraft Lodge 1746A records were transferred to the University of Connecticut Libraries on 11 May 1990, by Bill Shortell, President of the lodge.
Detailed Description
- Series I: By-Laws and Contracts, undated, 1969-1982
  - By-Laws: Lodge 1746A, 1969-1973 (Box 1:, Folder 1-3)
  - By-Laws: District 91, 1973 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Pension Plan Agreement, 1973-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws: Lodge 1746A, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Copies of by-law changes, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - IAMAW Constitution, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - By-Laws: Lodge 1746A, 1975-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 9-10)
  - Copies of by-law changes, 1976 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Contract Agreement, 1977 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - IAMAW Constitution, 1977 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Decisions, 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Contract Agreement, 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 15-16)
  - Amendment to contract, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration Decisions, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - By-Laws: 1746A, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Contract agreement, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - Constitution/Connecticut State AFL-CIO, 1980 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - Contract: Lodge 1746A, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
  - Contract agreement, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - Contract proposals, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 24-27)
  - Copies: agreement between IAM lodge 912 and General Electric, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
  - By-Laws: Auxiliary of Local 1746A, undated (Box 1:, Folder 29)
- Series II: Minutes, 1964-1983
  - Executive Board and membership meetings, 1964-1971 (Box 2:, Folder 30-37)
  - Attendance log: monthly membership Meetings, 1969 February - 1974 December (Box 2:, Folder 38-39)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 40)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 41)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 42)
  - District 91 Executive Board meetings, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 43)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 45)
  - Grand Lodge executive meeting, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 46)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 47)
  - District 91 Executive Board meetings, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder 48)
  - District 91 monthly membership meetings, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder 49)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder 50)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder 51)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder 52)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder 53)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder 56)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1977 (Box 2:, Folder 57)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1977 (Box 2:, Folder 58)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1977 (Box 2:, Folder 59)
  - District 91 Executive Board meetings, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 60)
  - District 91 monthly membership meetings, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 62)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder 65)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder 66)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 68)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 69)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 70)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 71)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 72)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 73)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 74)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 75)
  - Executive Board meetings, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 76)
  - Extraordinary meetings, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 77)
  - Monthly membership meetings, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 78)
- Series III: Office Files, 1970-1983
  - Membership Voting District #Numbers 5.6.7, 1970 (Box 3:, Folder 79)
  - Negotiations: agreement, purpose, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 80)
  - Negotiations: company proposals and work papers, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 81-82)
  - Political Action, 1972
    - Bristol (Box 3:, Folder 83)
    - Plainville (Box 3:, Folder 84)
    - Southington (Box 3:, Folder 85)
  - A. Philip Randolf Institute, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 86)
  - Aids for processing monthly membership reports, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 87)
  - Applications for discount auto insurance, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 88)
  - Applications returned from company, 1972-1973 (Box 3:, Folder 89)
  - Banks, letters to, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 90)
  - Calendar house schedule, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 91)
  - Cash members, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 92)
  - Change of status lists, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 93)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 94-95)
  - District Lodge 91: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 96-97)
  - Dropouts, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 98)
  - Festa, Alessio: Recording Secretary, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 99)
  - Glover, Eugene: General Secretary/Treasurer, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 100)
  - Grand Lodge: audit reports, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 101)
  - Grand Lodge: receipts and disbursements, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 102)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 103)
  - Insurance problems, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 104)
  - Layoff, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 105)
  - Machinists Non-Partisan Political League (M.N.P.P.L), 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 106)
  - Mailing list, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 107)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence: Lodge 1746A, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous Labor Union information, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 109)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 110)
  - New England Conference, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 111)
  - New member lists: monthly, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 112)
  - Political and Legislative information, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 113)
  - Population by shift, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 114)
  - Pratt and Whitney, letters from, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 115)
  - Put ons, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 116)
  - Quarterly configurations, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 117)
  - Rappa, Ralph: Personnel Supervisor, Pratt and Whitney: correspondence, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 118)
  - Safety Committee reports, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 119)
  - Senior Citizens, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 120)
  - Smith, Floyd, International President: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 121)
  - Steward's roster and areas, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 122)
  - Terminations, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 123)
  - Tinella, J.L.: President, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 124)
  - United Aircraft: correspondence, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 125)
  - Winisinger, William, Vice President: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 126)
  - Workman's Compensations hearings, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 127)
  - A. Philip Randolf Institute, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 128)
  - AFL-CIO: correspondence, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 129)
  - Albrycht, Irene: Recording Secretary, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 130)
  - Applications returned from company, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 131)
  - Attendance sheets: ratification meeting, 1974 Oct 22 (Box 3:, Folder 132)
  - Baseball, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 133)
  - Baseball excursion notices, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 134)
  - Calendar house schedules, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 135)
  - Canada: Lodge No. 510, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 136)
  - Cash members, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 137)
  - Change of status, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 138)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 139)
  - District 91: correspondence, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 140-140a)
  - Dropout information, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 141)
  - Dropout lists, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 142)
  - Entertainment Committee, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 143)
  - Farah strike, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 144)
  - Festa, Alessio: Treasurer, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 145)
  - Glover, Eugene: General Secretary/Treasurer, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 146)
  - Grand Lodge
    - Minutes of Executive Council meeting, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 147)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 148)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 149)
  - Grocery survey, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 150)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 151)
  - Iaccio, Sal: International Vice President, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 152)
  - International Aerospace Machinists Aerospace Conference, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 153)
  - Machinists Non-Partisan Political League, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 154)
  - Martel, Mildred, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 155)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 156)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence: Lodge 1746A, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 157)
  - Miscellaneous Union labor information, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 158)
  - Negotiations: correspondence, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 159)
  - Negotiations committee: names and addresses, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 160)
  - New England Conference, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 161)
  - New member lists: monthly, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 162)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 163)
  - Pictures, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 164)
  - Political activity: cable television, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 165)
  - Political legislation and information, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 166)
  - Population by shift, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 167)
  - Pratt and Whitney: correspondence, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 168)
  - Previous configurations and surveys, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 169)
  - Put ons, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 170)
  - Quarterly configurations, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 171)
  - Rappa, Ralph: Personnel Supervisor, Pratt and Whitney: correspondence, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 172)
  - Retired members, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 173)
  - Safety Committee reports, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 174)
  - Sample surveys and ballots, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 175)
  - Smith, Floyd, International President: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 176)
  - Steward, 1974
    - Address lists (Box 4:, Folder 177)
    - Christmas party (Box 4:, Folder 178)
    - Roster and areas (Box 4:, Folder 179)
  - Suggestion surveys, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 180)
  - Terminations, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 181)
  - Thank-you letters, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 182)
  - Tinella, Joseph: President, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 183)
  - United Aircraft: correspondence, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 184)
  - United Way, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 185)
  - Voter registration, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 186)
  - Winisinger, William, Vice President: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 187)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1974 (Box 4:, Folder 188)
  - Seniority list, 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 189-190)
  - A. Philip Randolf Institute, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 191)
  - AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 192)
  - Albrycht, Irene: Recording Secretary, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 193)
  - Applications: returned, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 194)
  - Cash members, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 195)
  - Change of status, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 196)
  - Committee Appointments, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 197)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 198)
  - Counsel referral forms, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 199)
  - District 91: correspondence, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 200-201)
  - Dropouts, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 202)
  - Education Committee, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 203)
  - Festa, Alessio: Treasurer, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 204)
  - Glover, Eugene: General Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 205-206)
  - Gordon: Attorney, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 207-208)
  - Grand Lodge: correspondence, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 209)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 210)
  - International Aerospace Machinists Aerospace Correspondence, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 211)
  - Machinists Non-Partisan Political League, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 212)
  - Mailing list, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 213)
  - Miscellaneous: incoming, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 214)
  - Miscellaneous: outgoing, 1975 (Box 4:, Folder 215)
  - New England Conference, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 216)
  - New member list, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 217)
  - Notes: miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 218)
  - Officers: Committee and Delegate appointments, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 219)
  - Photographs, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 220)
  - Political legislation and information, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 221)
  - Political information, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 222)
  - Population by shift, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 223)
  - Pratt and Whitney: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 224-225)
  - Put ons, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 226)
  - Rappa, Ralph E.: correspondence, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 227)
  - Retired members, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 228)
  - Safety Committee reports, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 229)
  - Smith, Floyd, International President: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 230-231)
  - Steward's information, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 232)
  - Softball information, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 233)
  - Surveys and Configurations, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 234)
  - Terminations, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 235)
  - Thank-you letters and cards, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 236)
  - Unions on strike: correspondence, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 237-238)
  - United Aircraft: correspondence, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 239)
  - United Way, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 240)
  - Winisinger, William, General Vice President: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5:, Folder 241-242)
  - A. Philip Randolf Institute, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 243)
  - American Arbitrations Association, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 244)
  - Applications: returned, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 245)
  - Cable Television issue, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 246)
  - Change of status, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 247)
  - Christmas Party, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 248)
  - Committee Appointments, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 249)
  - Community service, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 250)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 251)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 252)
  - Correspondence from other organizations, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 253)
  - District 91, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 254)
  - Dropout list, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 255)
  - Education Committee, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 256)
  - Employees service record, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 257)
  - Glover, Eugene: General Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 258-259)
  - Grand Lodge: correspondence, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 260)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 261)
  - Greater Meriden Labor Council, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 262)
  - IAM and UAW Legislative goals, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 263)
  - Insurance, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 264)
  - Machinists Non-Partisan Political League, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 265)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 266-267)
  - National Guard and Reserves, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 268)
  - New England Conference, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 269)
  - New member list, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 270)
  - Notes: miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 271)
  - Officers and Delegates, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 272)
  - Pictures and clippings, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 273)
  - Political information, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 274)
  - Population by shift, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 275)
  - Put ons, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 276)
  - Quarterly configurations, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 277)
  - Rappa, Ralph E.: outgoing correspondence, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 278)
  - Recreation Committee, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 279)
  - Retired members, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 280)
  - Scholarship Information, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 281)
  - Shea, Thomas: President:, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 282)
  - Steward's information, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 283)
  - Softball league, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 284)
  - Terminations, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 285)
  - Thank-you letters, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 286)
  - Tool and Die Conference, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 287)
  - Travel, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 288)
  - United Technologies Annual Report, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 289)
  - United Way, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 290)
  - Wage survey, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 291)
  - A. Philip Randolf Institute, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 292)
  - Applications: returned, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 293)
  - Baseball Committee, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 294)
  - Cash members list, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 295)
  - Change of status, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 296)
  - Christmas Party, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 297)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 298)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 299)
  - Costa, Anthony: Recording secretary, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 300)
  - District 91: all correspondence, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 301)
  - Dropout list, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 302)
  - Glover, Eugene: General Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 303-304)
  - Grand Lodge information, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 305)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 306)
  - Greater Meriden Labor Council, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 307)
  - Iaccio, Sal: General Vice President, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 308)
  - Labor Law Reform: letters to Congressmen, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 309)
  - Lodge Appointments, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 310)
  - Mailing lists, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 311)
  - Merit wages, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 312)
  - Miscellaneous information, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 313)
  - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 314)
  - New England Conference, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 315)
  - New member lists, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 316)
  - Peretta, James F.: Personnel Supervisory, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 317)
  - Peretta, James F.: correspondence, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 318-320)
  - Pictures and clippings, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 321)
  - Population by shift, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 322)
  - Put ons, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 323)
  - Quarterly configurations, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 324)
  - Retired members, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 325)
  - Sample mailings, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 326)
  - Shea, Thomas: correspondence, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 327)
  - Softball league, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 328)